NICOLAI THOMSEN

DATA SCIENCE STUDENT | RESEARCH ASSISTANT

PROFILE

Since a start in IT-based startups I've worked with business development, IT project management, IT consultancy and data analytics. In 2020, I'm focusing on enhancing my data science capabilities, particularly within machine learning, statistical principles and advanced data analysis.

EXPERIENCE

NLP RESEARCH ASSISTANT

CBS | Dept. of Mgmt., Society & Comms. | 09/2019 -

- ML-based pattern detection in natural language
- Data cleansing, data wrangling, regex

BUSINESS ANALYST

Deloitte | Tech, Strategy & Transformation | 09/2019 – 03/2020

- Deliverables within IT strategy, finance and IT op. models
- Big Data & AA community | Chatbot community
- Development / configuration of chatbot(s)

CRM QUALITY ASSESSMENT MANAGER

Simply | STARTUP | 09/2016 - 01/2017

- Management of Bangalore-based software developers
- Testing of Simply's CRM system pre and post launch

IT PROJECT MANAGER & COMMS. LEAD

Boardmeter | STARTUP | 06/2016 – 06/2018

- IT P.M., business dev. strategy, interim CEO '17 '18
- Onboarding and evaluation of high-profile companies

OTHER

CONTENT CREATOR @ <u>Talentguiden</u> | FREDERIKSBERG | 16 Company portrait articles

PRESIDENT @ CBS Code | FREDERIKSBERG | 07/19 – Management | Front-end dev. | Fundraising & partnerships

VOLUNTEER @ Finn Nørgaard Foreningen | KBH K | 02/18 – Front-end dev. | Content creation | Event staff

VOLUNTEER @ <u>TEDxCopenhagen</u> | KBH K | 10/19 IT staff | Event staff



CONTACT



EDUCATION

BACHELOR'S DEGREE (2016 – 2019)

BA. & Information Technology
Copenhagen Business School

5TH Semester @ San Diego State University

CURRENT (2019 - 2021)

MSc. BA & IT – Data Science
Copenhagen Business School

CERTIFICATIONS

ITIL® Foundation V3 | Boost.ai® Advanced AI Trainer | Boost.ai® AI Trainer | (Udemy)

EXTRACURRICULAR COURSES

TENSORFLOW FOR DEEP LEARNING

TensorFlow / Keras | Udemy | 2019

PYTHON FOR DATA SCIENCE AND MACHINE LEARNING BOOTCAMP

Python / SK-Learn | Udemy | 2019

WINDOWS PROGRAMMING

C# | San Diego State University | 2018

COMPLETE C# MASTERCLASS

C# / LINQ | Udemy | 2018

COMPLETE JAVASCRIPT COURSE

JavaScript | Udemy | 2017

COMPLETE JAVA MASTERCLASS

Java | Udemy | 2017